(Sheldon:)You continue to underestimate
my capabilities, madam.
(Penny:)Okay, let me put it this way.
If you're Leonard's friend...
(Penny:)...you will support him
no matter who he wants to be with.
(Sheldon:)Wait a minute.
Why am I doing all the giving here?
(Sheldon:)If Leonard's really my friend...
(Sheldon:)...why doesn't he have to support me
in my hatred of Leslie Winkle?
(Penny:)Because love trumps hate.
(Sheldon:)Oh, now you're just making stuff up.
Okay. Good night, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Mario.
(Sheldon:)If only I could control everyone
the way I control you.
(Sheldon:)Hop, you little plumber, hop, hop, hop.
(Sheldon(entering):)When the two of you reach a natural
stopping point, I'd like to have a word.
If the word is "pee-pee," just do it.